A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Grants, Accession 2015:115 FA1321
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grants, 1979-2007; 1
  - Temple University - Beyond Acting White: Reframing the Debate on Black Student Achievement - Manuscript - 10301523, 2005 (Box 44, Folder 320-322)
  - The Asian American Journalists Association (AAJA) - 09701352, 2001-2003 (Box 44, Folder 323)
    Boot Camp by the Bay: Training and Developing the Next Generation of Journalists of Color, July 28-August 1, University of San Francisco, San Francisco, CA; AAJA 2003 Strategic Planning Initiative
  - Smith College - Meridians: Feminism, Race, Transnationalism - 09900983, 2000-2002 (Box 44, Folder 324)
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York - New York City Social Indicators Survey - 09901399, 1999 (Box 44, Folder 325)
    Assets/Human Development Research Paper (?) (HDRP)
  - Terralingua - Draft Framework for an Index of Biocultural Diversity - Draft - 10101379, 2002 October (Box 44, Folder 326)